The next game we're going to talk about is called lazy pineapple.
Lazy pineapple is one of three variations of the game pineapple.
Lazy pineapple is dealt out just like pineapple, with each player receiving three down cards.
However, in lazy pineapple the players will discard their card after the flop.
Let's see how lazy pineapple is dealt out.
Each player receives three down cards from the dealer.
Once these three cards are dealt out to each player, a betting round will start with the player to the left of the dealer.
Once that betting round is over, the dealer will burn a card and turn the first three cards to the community, called the flop.
Since this is lazy pineapple, this is where each player will look at their hand and make a decision to fold a card.
Once each player has folded a card from their hand, this leaves him with two hole cards and a betting round starts.
The betting round starts again with the player to the left of the dealer.
Once that betting round is over, the dealer will burn a card and turn the fourth card to the community, called the flop.
I'm sorry, that's called the turn.
The betting round will start with the player to the left of the dealer, and once that betting round is over, the dealer will burn a card and turn the last card to the community, called the river.
In lazy pineapple, the best five-card hand wins.
So, the players will turn their cards over using their best five cards from their two hole cards and the five community cards to make their best five-card hand.
And that's how lazy pineapple is played.